JAMIE GARCIA Frontend Developer

4 years of experience developing with javascript frameworks such as Vue.js, React.js and Typescript. Have developed content with WordPress using Elementor and Avada. Familiar with Python, C#, SQL, and REST APIs. Capable of Agile/Scrum project management. Motivated and self-sufficient. Able to communicate effectively and promptly. Currently in school for my Bachelors in Computer Science with WGU.

Skills

- HTML
- WordPress, Elementor, Avada
- CSS/ SASS/Tailwind/Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- JQuery
- Vue.js, Nuxt.js, React.js, Next.js
- Redux/Saga/Vuex store
- Version Control: Git, Github, Bitbucket
- Python

Github: https://github.com/JamieGarcia123

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jamiegarcia123456789/

Portfolio: jamiegarcia.dev

Experience

Impact Group Marketing/ Web Developer

March 2024 - PRESENT, Boerne, TX (remote)

Developing websites with WordPress, DotNetNuke, Shopify, SquareSpace, and WIX. Implement plugins or custom code. Optimize sites for S.E.O. ranking.

Codesulting / Front End Developer

April 2018 - January 2024, Boerne, TX (remote)

Work with clients and back end developers. Use design programs mock ups from Figma. Set up HTML emails with hubspot or sendgrid when needed. Utilize resources and knowledge to develop and learn desired frameworks for clients.

Certifications

AWS Cloud Practitioner

December 2023

WGU/ AWS

CompTia Project+

February 2024

WGU/CompTia

ITIL 4 Foundations

August 2024

People Cert

Education

Western Governors University

1-1-2023 - current, Salt Lake City, UT (remote)

Studying for a Bachelors of Science, Software Development to include but not limited to: SQL, AWS, HTML5, Python.